grimsbytelegraph.co.uk 2012-12-30

# This is Grimsby | Privacy Policy

Effective from 16 May 2012

This privacy policy applies only to this website (the "Site"). If you do not accept this privacy policy, you must not use this Site.

**Collection Of Personal Information**

We collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you complete registration or enquiry forms, submit comments to the Site, participate in message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities or send emails or text messages to us. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it. 

**Use of Cookies**

In addition to personal information you provide, we may also collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site or access content in our electronic communications with you.

The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the Site or within electronic communications. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. Cookies allow us to identify your computer and find out details about your visit and browsing habits so that we can offer you a more personalised experience and manage, monitor and improve services.

Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, you may not be able to use some of the core features of the Site. CLICK HERE for instructions on controlling cookies in the most recent version of Windows Explorer (Users of other browsers should contact their manufacturer for instructions).

The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not personally identifiable, it only includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the internet e.g. operating system and platform, IP address, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on the Site and geographical location.

Display advertising on the Site is provided by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners will serve advertisements that they believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to the Site and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, email address or telephone number). For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising please visit [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/)

For more detail on our cookies, and on trusted 3rd party companies using cookies on our Site please **click here**

You can learn more about cookies and how to reject cookies using different types of browser by visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Separate tools are also available for managing local shared objects or ‘Flash cookies’ from the [Adobe website](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html). These cookies may be used to manage the effective delivery of services using video or other flash related content. 

For more information on how cookies are used on this site please click here

**Use Of Your Information**

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which shall include (without limitation): • Verifying your identity (for example when you return to the Site);  
• Personalising your visits to the Site to improve the services provided to you;  
• Informing you about the latest changes to the Site, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting;  
• customer service and support;  
• Enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using our Email a friend and Share this article functionality;  
• Communicating (and personalising such communication) with you;  
• Conducting market research; and/or  
• carrying out technical and statistical analysis to measure the performance of our services and the Site.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We may share information about you with suppliers that we engage to help us provide certain services and/or functionality e.g online payment processing. We will use reasonable endeavours to control and be responsible for the use of your information by such suppliers. Furthermore, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (which may not provide the same protection for such information as the European Economic Area provides) in the event that the processing of your information involves such a transfer.

We may disclose your information (including personal information) to other companies within the Daily Mail and General Trust plc group of companies (the “DMGT Group”, see [www.dmgt.co.uk](http://www.dmgt.co.uk/) for further information) and may use and share within the DMGT Group information that we learn from your interactions with us and other companies within the DMGT Group.

Subject to your consent, your personal information may be used by us and/or other companies within the DMGT Group to contact you by email, fax, telephone, SMS and/or post with information and offers on products/services provided by us and/or other companies within the DMGT Group. 

Subject to your consent, we may supply personal information about you to selected third parties so that they may contact you with information and offers which may be of interest to you.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws and government or regulatory bodies’ lawful requests for information. 

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.

**Message Boards, Blogs and Other Public Forums**

The Site makes message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities available to users of the Site and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our Site becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information. For more information, please click on the Site's Terms and House Rules.

**Email A Friend And Share This Article Facilities**

When you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (e.g. the name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details. Keeping Your Personal Information Secure.

We take the security of your personal information very seriously and have appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures in place to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure as required by law in England.

**Accessing Your Personal Information**

If you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, change your marketing preferences or have any other queries about this privacy policy, please write to us (including full details of your request) at the following address:

This Is  
Northcliffe Media Limited  
Northcliffe House  
2 Derry Street  
London  
W8 5TT

We may charge a small administration fee (not exceeding the maximum permitted by law) in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If we change this privacy policy, we will post the revised privacy policy here with an updated effective date. If we make significant changes to the privacy policy, we may also notify you by other means such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.
